

RESUME ARGHYAPOLLEY

PROFILE

I am a skilled Full Stack Engineer with strong 4.7 yrs. of experience in Web App development using JavaScript, React, and Node. In addition, have 2 yrs. of experience Predictive and Forecasting Modelling, Text Mining, and Chatbot. I worked on various domains such as Finance, Automobile, and Ecommerce.

CONTACT



arghyapolley@gmail.com



9611412793



Bangalore, India



www.github.com/arghyapolley

EDUCATION

West Bengal University of Technology B.Techin Electronics & Communication, 2013

TECHNOLOGY

JavaScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit-Learn, Scipy, Alexa, Rasa, OpenCV,

EXPERIENCE

Pramati Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Development Engineer

May 2018 - Present, Hyderabad, India

Track agent performance using various parameters like AHT, Productivity, Repeat Calls, First Call resolution etc. in a customer care. Also call volume forecasting using ARIMAX and Text Mining on customers Feedback – Sentiment Analysis and topic modeling.

Build a chatbot from scratch and deployed it for one of the leading market research Co.

Developed Scalable Web App using React, Redux, Node, and MongoDB. I responsible for the React as well as NodeJS.

Tagos Design Innovation Pvt. Ltd., Software Engineer

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018, Bangalore, India

Worked on eCommerce domain for product discovery used JS, React and Redux.

RE Power(SIT Project), Application Manager Oct 2016– March 2017, Bangalore, India

Involved in product development from scratch for in-house product development using React with Redux, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript.

Webfosys Networks (P) Ltd, Website Developer June 2015 – Sep 2016, Bangalore, India

Worked on ecommerce web app using React, Redux.